cartooncrazy.net 2016-05-27

# Privacy Policy - www.cartooncrazy.net

This privacy policy tells you ways we use individual know-how collected at this web site. Please learn this privacy coverage earlier than utilizing the web site or submitting any private knowledge. By means of using the web site, you receive the practices described here.

**Advertising**  
We use 3rd party advertising firms to serve ads whilst you visit our web page. These corporations could use aggregated knowledge (now not together with your title, tackle, e mail handle or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites to be able to furnish ads about items and offerings of interest to you. If you want more expertise about this apply and to know your alternatives about now not having this expertise used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example, to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
Our site may use cookies and tracking technology which are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to collect information in the course of serving ads to you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

**Distribution of Information**  
We do not share your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized staff of this site (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: Contact US

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
